A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, SG 1.27 (A2001) FA488
Rockefeller Archive Center
- AC.2001.083: Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, 1987-2000; AC.2001.083; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF), AC.2001.083.1; 11.79 Cubic Feet 9 record storage boxes
    - RF 93022 #218 - HUNAN MEDICAL UNIVERSITY (CHINA) - TRANSFORMING GENE OF NASOPHARYNGEAL CARCINOMA, 1992-2000 (Box R3432)
    - RF 93024 #1 - NORTH CAROLINA STATE UNIVERSITY - SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURAL SYSTEMS, 1989-1995 (Box R3432)
    - RF 93024 #3 - EMPRESA BRASILEIRA DE PESQUISA AGROPECUARIA (EMBRAPA) (BRAZIL) - ON-FARM TESTING OF AGROFORESTRY AND SLASH AND BURN CULTIVATION, 1993-1998 (Box R3432)
    - RF 93027 #431 - EMORY UNIVERSITY - EXPENSES RELATED TO INCLEN ENVIRONMENTAL AND OCCUPATIONAL HEALTH INITIATIVE, 1990-2000 (Box R3432)
    - RF 93028 #17 - MAKERERE UNIVERSITY (UGANDA) - B.SC. NURSING PROGRAM FOR "WOMEN FOR WOMEN'S HEALTH INITIATIVE", 1992-1999 (Box R3432)
    - RF 93031 #518 - BENTI, GETAHUN - ADIA: DYNAMICS OF MIGRATION TO ADDIS ABABA AND OVER-URBANIZATION OF THE CITY, c. 1941-1974, 1995-1998 (Box R3432)
    - RF 93031 #525 - WAMBUGUH, OSCAR - ADIA: LOCAL COMMUNITIES AND WILDLIFE IN KENYA, 1994-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #527 - MUKOYA-WANGIA, SABINA- ADIA: MAIZE AMONG KENYAN FARMERS, 1993-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #534 - ALAWY, ABDILLAHI - ADIA: STRATEGIES FOR FOOD PRODUCTION AND ENVIRONMENTAL CONSERVATION IN KENYA, 1995-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #536 - DESTA, SOLOMON - ADIA: BANKING LIVESTOCK CAPITAL AND URBAN DEVELOPMENT IN ETHIOPIA, 1995-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #538 - MBILIZI, MARGARET - ADIA: GENDER SOCIALIZATION IN EDUCATION OF MALAWIAN GIRLS, 1995-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #540 - ELOUDOU-ENYEGUE, PARFAIT - ADIA: FERTILITY RESPONSES TO ECONOMIC RECESSION IN CAMEROON, 1995-2000 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #543 - ESIKURI, ENOS - ADIA: LAND USE CHANGES IN SAVANNA WILDLIFE OF KENYA, 1995-1999 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #545 - JERANYAMA, PETER - ADIA: SMALLHOLDER CROPPING SYSTEMS OF ZIMBABWE, 1995-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #554 - CHABATAMA, MEBBIENES - ADIA: THE STATE AND FOOD SECURITY IN ZAMBIA, 1899-1996, 1995-1999 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #556 - YEBOAH, KWAKU - ADIA: CHILD SURVIVAL AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH OF ADOLESCENTS IN GHANA, 1995-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #559 - GAKONYO, NJERI - ADIA: STRUCTURE OF ZIMBABWEAN WHOLESALE VEGETABLE MARKETS, 1995-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #563 - RANDRIANASOLO, ARMAND- ADIA: SYSTEMATICS AND EVOLUTION OF THREE GENERA OF MALAGASY ANACARDIACEASE, 1995-1998 (Box R3433)
    - RF 93031 #565 - KAPRAN, ISSOUFOU - ADIA: GENETIC ANALYSIS OF MATURITY IN GRAIN SORGHUM, 1995-1998 (Box R3434)
    - RF 93031 #571 - KASSAYE, TARIK - ADIA: EFFECT OF VITAMIN A ON MORBIDITY FROM LOWER RESPIRATORY INFECTIONS, 1996-1999 (Box R3434)
    - RF 93042 #19 - TULANE UNIVERSITY - CYCLOPS TO CONTROL AEDES AEGYPTI MOSQUITO, 1991-1994 (Box R3434)
    - RF 93042 #26 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - AEDES AEGYPTI CONTROL, 1987-1998 (Box R3434)
    - RF 93042 #26 - PAN AMERICAN HEALTH ORGANIZATION - AEDES AEGYPTI CONTROL - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1987-1998 (Box R3434)
    - RF 93042 #28 - MEXICAN HEALTH FOUNDATION- AEDES AEGYPTI CONTROL PROGRAM, 1990-1998 (Box R3435)
    - RF 93042 #28 - MEXICAN HEALTH FOUNDATION- AEDES AEGYPTI CONTROL PROGRAM - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-1998 (Box R3435)
    - RF 93042 #30 - UNIVERSITY OF ARIZONA - AEDES AEGYPTIIN MEXICO AND HONDURAS, 1995-1999 (Box R3435)
    - RF 93044 #38 - WEST CHINA UNIVERSITY OF MEDICAL SCIENCES - STUDY OF JAPANESE ENCEPHALITIS VACCINE, 1992-1997 (Box R3435)
    - RF 93045 #13 - K.E.M. HOSPITAL RESEARCH CENTRE (INDIA) - ADOLESCENT SEXUALITY AND FERTILITY IN WESTERN MAHARASHTRA, 1995-1998 (Box R3435)
    - RF 93053 #183 - DAR A LUZ - THE HISTORY OF INFAMY, 1994-2000 (Box R3436)
    - RF 93059 #13 - UN/WHO - IMMUNIZATION AND VACCINOLOGY, 1990-1998 (Box R3436)
    - RF 93061 - EXPLORATIONS- HEALTH AND THE ENVIRONMENT, 1991-1998 (Box R3436)
    - RF 93065 #44 - WORLD VISION, INC. - GIRLS' EDUCATION AND DEVELOPMENT IN KENYA, 1992-2000 (Box R3436)
    - RF 93065 #58 - KANNAE, LAWRENCE A. - RE-ENTRY AWARD: EDUCATIONAL ACHIEVEMENT OF GIRLS IN GHANA, 1994-1997 (Box R3436)
    - RF 93065 #61 - AFRICAN ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - FEMALE EDUCATION IN AFRICA, 1989-1998 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93065 #61 - AFRICAN ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - FEMALE EDUCATION IN AFRICA - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1989-1998 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93065 #62 - UNIVERSITY OF DARES SALAAM (TANZANIA) - STRENGTHEN GIRLS' PARTICIPATION IN SCIENCE AND MATH IN SECONDARY SCHOOLS, 1993-1997 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93066 #47 - MALAWI INSTITUTE OF EDUCATION - VIDEO SCIENCE PROJECT, 1991-1999 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93066 #50 - KAGERA WRITERS AND PUBLISHERS CO-OPERATIVE SOCIETY (TANZANIA) - NEWSPAPER SUPPLEMENT FOR YOUTH, 1995-1996 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93066 #51 - ZIMBABWE TRUST (ENGLAND) - "ACTION MAGAZINE", TO DEVELOP A MARKETING STRATEGY, 1994-2000 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93066 #53 - UNIVERSITY OF IBADAN (NIGERIA) - MOTIVATING STUDENTS TO LEARN SCIENCE, 1995-1997 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93067 #12 - ESPERANZA PEACE AND JUSTICE CENTER - "LEADERSHIP/ACTIVIST TRAINING PROGRAM", 1994-1998 (Box R3437)
    - RF 93072 - GREATER KANSAS CITY COMMUNITY FOUNDATION- NATIONAL COALITION FOR YOUTH TRANSITION, 1990-2000 (Box R3438, Box R3439)
    - RF 93072 - GREATER KANSAS CITY COMMUNITY FOUNDATION- NATIONAL COALITION FOR YOUTH TRANSITION - SUPPLEMENTARY MATERIAL, 1990-2000 (Box R3438, Box R3439)
    - RF 93078 #4 - NIRAULA, BHANU B. - WOMEN'S AUTONOMY AND REPRODUCTIVE HEALTH IN NEPAL, 1996-1998 (Box R3439)
    - RF 94001 #228 - M.G. SCIENCE INSTITUTE (INDIA) - CAROTENOID BIOSYNTHESIS IN RICE ENDOSPERM, 1992-2000 (Box R3439)
    - RF 94001 #236 - HUAZHONG AGRICULTURAL UNIVERSITY - PHOTOPERIOD SENSITIVE MALE STERILITY IN RICE, 1990-2000 (Box R3439)
    - RF 94001 #239 - CHINESE ACADEMY OF SCIENCES - GENES TRANSFERENCE INTO RICE, 1990-1999 (Box R3439)